Quadri Oloruntomiwa Emmanuel

Software Engineer

Talented Software Development leader experienced in producing and updating Scalable and Maintainable systems. Optimized structures and processes to accomplish customer targets and promote company loyalty. Expert in diverse programming languages, including Javascript (React, Node & Express), PHP (Laravel) and many more.

Work History

2020-01 - Freelance Software Developer

Current Self Employed

Providing clients with highly scalable, performant and maintainable applications and websites

2019-11 - Fullstack Software Engineer

2020-04 Wildfire, Lagos, Lagos

- Collaborated on all stages of systems development lifecycle, from requirement gathering to production releases.
- Administered, supported and monitored databases by proactively resolving database issues and maintaining servers.
- Coordinated with project management staff on database development timelines and project scope.
- Delivered and maintained scalable system architecture to support high-availability Internet site with various internal
 applications.
- · Led version control efforts for Wildfire, employing GitHub and other public and open source repositories.

Education

2017-09 - Associate of Science: Computer Science

2019-07 Gateway Polytechnic ICT Saapade - Remo, Ogun Nigeria.

Writing

In my free times, i enjoy writing about things around me and showing others my perspective of the world through my writings.

Contact

Address

Lagos, LA

Phone

08067163832

E-mail

bendamyth@gmail.com

lwitte

https://twitter.com/tomiwa _quadri

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/i n/ade-tomiwa-22504b1b9/

www

https://adethormiwa.github .io

Skills

Algorithm implementation



Testing and maintenance



engineering

.....

Database management software

••••

•

Solutions deployment

HTML and XML

•

Database programming

Portable code writer

••••

Software Development

••••

Web Security

••••

JavaScript

••••